剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
他们认为你很特别
We think you're special.
我们需要你带领一批高素质的人员
We want you to lead a team of highly trained people.
-面试怎么样了?  -为什么我要跑去波特兰
-How was the interview?  -Why I'd want to go all the way to Portland
去做那些或许根本不可能的研究工作
for research that doesn't even work?
你成功了 我怀孕了
Because it does work. I'm pregnant.
我这一辈子就是想要个孩子 现在因为你  我的梦想实现了
My whole life, all I've ever wanted was to have a baby.and now because of you,I can.
我知道你不在乎 可那些
I know that you don't care,but the people
和我一起生活了三年的人 就这样把我扔下了
I spent the last three years of my life with...they just left me.
-你还好吗? -还好
-You okay?  -Yeah.
-她不能一起来  -不  她能
-She is not coming with us.  -Yes, she is.
-为什么?  -因为她也被丢下了
-Why?  -They left her behind, too.
已经很晚了
It's getting late.
我们就在这里扎营吧
This is a good place to make camp.
我去找些柴火来
I'll get some firewood.
我跟你一起去
I'll go with you.
你想谈谈吗?
Do you wanna talk about it?
谈什么?
Talk about what?
关于你和他们一起生活的这一个星期
About the week you spent over there with them.
你走后...
Well, after you left,
我...
I'd...
我和他们做了笔交易 如果我照顾好Ben
I'd made a deal with them... If I took care of Ben,
他们会让我离开这座岛
that they'd let me off the island.
我也不知道是不是真的 我就低调行事
I don't know. I just kept my head down,
做我该做的
did what I was supposed to,
不问任何问题
and I didn't ask any questions.
就这些了吗?
And that's it?
就这些了
That's it.
好吧  我们来谈谈
Okay. Let's have it.
我想知道你们那些人在这个岛上做什么
I want to know what you people are doing on this island,
你们为什么要恐吓我们
why you're terrorizing us,
列出什么名单 还绑架儿童
making lists, kidnapping children.
我想知道一切
I want to know everything.
但首先我想知道的是...
But the first thing I'd like to know is...
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是Juliet Burke 我约了Mittleos生物科学
I'm Juliet Burke. I'm with Mittelos Bioscience.
-我会通知Alpert先生的  -谢谢
-I'll let Mr.Alpert know you're here.  -Thank you.
他们把"商业机密"看的很重
they're taking this whole "corporate secrecy" thing a little too seriously.
我永远也不会像他们一样
I'm never gonna fit in with these people.
你好 Burke医生
Hey there, Dr.Burke.
-请你打开后车厢  我来帮你拿行李  -谢谢
-If you pop the trunk, I'll get your bags.  -Thank you.
你终于找到我们了
You managed to find us.
-我根本不知道这里还有机场  -这让所有人都很惊讶
-I didn't even know they had an airport out here.  -I know. It surprises everyone.
-你一定是Rachel  -很高兴见到你
-You must be Rachel.  -Nice to meet you.
谢谢你让我们借用你姐姐几个月
Thank you for letting us borrow your sister for a few months.
答应我让她完好无损的回来
Just promise me you'll bring her back in one piece.
我们尽力而为吧
Well, we'll do our best.
我们要保持商业机密...
So listen, it's a... security thing, you know?
我们来陪你走剩下的路吧...
We have to take you in the rest of the way, so...
只要你准备好了 我们随时等着
Whenever you're ready, we'll be waiting right over here,
不用着急 很高兴见到你
but please take your time. Pleasure to meet you.
-谢谢  -谢谢你
-Thanks.  -Thank you.
最好这样
It's better this way.
这样做错了吗?
Is this a mistake?
我不该走 如果你又病了该怎么办?
I shouldn't go. What if you get sick again?
不会的  癌症已经好了
I won't. The cancer's gone,
多亏你  我怀上了
and I'm 100% preggers, thanks to you.
-我会回来的...  -我知道
-I'll be back...  -Yes, I know.
在你生孩子之前 我保证
Before you give birth. I promise.
别担心我们好吗? 好的
I know. Don't worry about us, okay?
你已经走到了这一步...
You spent your whole life working to get here, so...
千万别搞砸了
don't blow it.
-我爱你  -我爱你
-I love you.  -I love you.
去吧 为你骄傲
Go make us proud.
再见了
Bye.
你是谁?
Who are you?
如果我告诉你
If I told you who I was,
如果我告诉你我知道的一切
if I told you everything that I know,
你会杀了我的
you'd kill me.
如果你不说 你猜我会怎么做?
What do you think I'll do if you don't?
别说了
Leave her alone.
迟早她会回答我的问题
Sooner or later, she'll answer my questions.
当她准备好时她会说的
She'll answer your questions when she's ready,
而你只能等着
and you'll wait until she is.
我会保护她
She's under my protection.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
Claire?
怎么了?
What is it?
好了  不哭了
It's okay.
Claire
你还好吗?
You okay?
Chaile
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
-你没听见Aaron吗?  -他还好吗?
-Didn't you hear Aaron?  -Is he okay?
他很好 你没事吧?
No, he's okay, he's okay.Are you all right?
我只是感到有点头晕
Yeah, I just...feel a little bit off.
大概没睡好
I didn't sleep well.
真不敢相信我没听见他哭
I can't believe I didn't hear him crying.
也许有些感冒了吧
Maybe you're coming down with something.
还是让我来照顾Aaron
But why don't you let me take Aaron,
-你好好休息一下吧  -你不介意吧?
-and you get some more rest?  -Yeah, do you mind?
当然
Absolutely.
我不会睡很久的
I won't sleep... long.
我猜让他们就这样等 应该没什么用吧
I guess it's no use asking them to wait up, huh?
他们会接受你的 给他们点时间
They'll come around. Just give them some time.
我们的人把Sayid锁在秋千上三天
My people kept Sayid chained to a swing set for three days.
然后我拽着Kate来到丛林
Then I dragged Kate into the jungle,
把她和我拷在一起 还撒了谎
handcuffed myself to her and lied about it.
他们还需要时间想吗?
How much time do you think they need?
还有几小时就到海滩了
We'll be back to our beach a couple hours.
那时候他们大概就接受你了
They'll probably be over it by then.
你紧张吗?
You nervous?
当然
Hell, yes.
我知道六个月确实很长
I know that six months sounds like an eternity,
但在那里
but you're gonna be amazed
你会感到时间过的很快
at how time flies once you're there.
我迫不及待的想知道 我们要去哪儿了?
I can't wait to find out where "there" is.
Burke医生 请坐吧
Dr.Burke, wanna have a seat?
我要给你做下体检
I'd like to take some of your vitals,
如果你不介意的话
if that's okay with you.
当然  没问题
Yeah, sure.
公司的每个人都很期待
Everyone at the company is really excited
你的到来 Burke医生
about you coming down, Dr.Burke,
而你的研究成果
and I think your research
将会对我们的工程有很大的推动
is really gonna have a major impact on us.
那是什么?
What is that?
那是橙汁  加了一定计量的安眠药
That is orange juice with a considerable amount of tranquilizer mixed in.
你想让我喝了它?
You want me to drink it?
这一路上你一定会想睡觉的 Burke医生
Oh, yes. You're gonna want to be asleep for the trip, Dr.Burke.
那会很颠簸的
It can be kind of intense.
我在你们的合同上签了字
I was fine with signing all of your paperwork,
还同意在六个月里
fine with agreeing to not talk
不和我生活中的任何人说话
to anyone in my life for six months,
接受在医学界
fine with the fact that no one in the medical community
-没有一个人听说过Mittelos这个公司  -你为什么会接受?
-has ever heard of Mittelos Bioscience  -Why were you fine?
-什么?  -你为什么会接受那些的?
-What?  -Why were you fine with those things?
这看起来像是你工作的一个巨大的转折点
It seems like quite a leap for a job opportunity,
而且我们给你的报酬也不是很多
and we're not paying you that much.
我想是因为在你内心深处
I think you're fine because deep down, a part of you knows
告诉你 我们要带你去的地方很特别
that the place we're taking you to is special.
特别?
Special, huh?
问你个问题 Juliet
Let me ask you something, Juliet.
你让一个女人 你的亲妹妹
You took a woman... Your own sister,
一个生殖系统被化疗破坏
whose reproductive system was ravaged by chemotherapy,
一个不能生育的人 你让她怀孕了
who is sterile, and you made her pregnant.
你创造了本不该被创造的生命
You created life where life wasn't supposed to be.
这是一种天赋 Juliet
That's a gift, Juliet.
你有这种天赋
You have a gift.
做一些不平凡的事吗?
to do something significant with it?
我们要去的地方 你就可以做到这些
Where we're going, you can do just that.
我们到底要去哪儿?
Where exactly are we going?
我还不能告诉你
I can't tell you that,
但我能告诉你
but what I can tell you is that
你将在那里见到
you'll see things there
你从未想象到的东西
that you never imagined.
没人强迫你做任何事
Now no one is forcing you to do anything,
如果你改变主意的话
so if you change your mind,
我们很乐意送你回去...
we're happy to take you back to...
你不该喝那么快的
You probably shouldn't have drunk that so fast.
早上好
Good morning.
没事的  你会在接下来的几个小时里感到嗓子很难受
No, no, it's okay. You'll be hoarse for a few hours,
但会慢慢好起来的
but it gets better as the day goes on.
很抱歉绑着你
Sorry I had to strap you in,
但最后一段路程总有些颠簸
but the last leg is always a little bumpy.
小心你的头 把手给我
Watch your head. Give me your hand.
我们到了
We're here.
到哪儿了?
Here where?
你好 Burke医生
Hello, Dr.Burke.
我叫Benjamin Linus
My name is Benjamin Linus.
我很期待与你合作
I'm really looking forward to working with you.
注意脚下
Watch your step here.
水太多了
Hey, that's too much water.
会很稀的
It's gonna be all soggy.
这是燕麦片  伙计 当然要稀的才好
It's oatmeal, dude. It's supposed to be soggy.
这不是三个爸爸和一个小娃娃嘛
Well, if it ain't three men and a baby.
我把Hugo算两个人
I counted Hugo twice.
又怎么了? 我又没叫你绰号
Oh, what? Come on. I used your name.
这里还有阿斯匹林吗?
Does anybody know where there's any aspirin?
Clarie 你脸色很差
Claire, you don't look so good.
你起来干什么? 你应该在休息的
What are you doing up? You're meant to be in bed.
我知道  只是我感到头很沉
Yeah, no, I know. My head is pounding.
交给我吧  两片阿斯匹林马上送到
I got you covered. Two aspirin coming right up.
谢谢
Thank you.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
Jack  是Jack!
Jack! It's Jack!
快来啊  是Jack!
Come on! Come on! It's Jack!
是Jack
It's Jack.
Sayid!
Hurley!
医生
Doctor.
她在这里干什么?
What the hell is she doing here?
那么说...
So...
你是他们的人咯?
You're, like, one of them, huh?
我叫Juliet
I'm Juliet.
我不记得在码头见过你...
I don't remember you from the dock...
在那里你们用袋子套住我们的头...
Where you put bags on our heads...
你们吓到了我们
After you shocked us.
我那天休息
I had the day off.
听说你是个医生
So I hear you're a doctor.
其实我是个研究人员
I'm really more of a researcher.
他们让你来盯着我?
They send you over here to keep an eye on me?
好吧
Ok.
你们的一个人 Ethan...
The last one of you guys that came over here... Ethan...
他绑架了Clarie Charlie很生气
He kidnapped Claire, and Charlie got upset.
我们把他埋在那边
We buried him over there.
她死了 Juliet  她死了
She's gone, Juliet. She's dead.
没关系的  你尽力了
It's okay. You tried.
你干嘛不去休息一下呢?
Why don't you go ahead and take off?
我会和Ben说的
I'll talk to Ben.
怀孕是Sabine自己的决定
It was Sabine's choice to get pregnant.
她知道要承担风险的
She knew she was taking a risk.
我认为是怀孕时发生的
I think it happens at conception,
我就无能为力了
there's nothing I can do about it,
-至少是在这里  -我不是很明白
-at least not here.  -I'm not sure I understand.
唯一的办法是
The only way to see if I'm right
带她离开这个岛 回到迈阿密
is to take a woman off the island, back to Miami.
不  你不能把任何人带离这座岛
No. You're not taking anybody off the island.
如果这样的话 我就无能为力了
In that case, there's thing more I can do.
我知道你对我寄予厚望 Ben
I know you put a lot of faith in me, Ben,
我很抱歉帮不了你
and I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
我妹妹三个月后就要生产了...
My sister's giving birth in three months...
而我连个电话也没打给过她
and I haven't even been able to call her.
是时候让我回家了
It's time for me to go home.
你妹妹生不了孩子了 Juliet
Your sister won't be giving birth in three months, Juliet.
在这之前她就会死
She'll be dead before then.
她的癌症又复发了
Her cancer's back.
-你从哪里弄到这些的?  -Mikhail 我很抱歉 我早该告诉你的
-Where did you get this?  -Mikhail.Sorry.I should have told you sooner.
我只是不知道有什么好处...
But I didn't see what good it would do...
有什么好处?! 我本该回家的!
What good it would do?! Could have gone home!
-我本该和她在一起!  -你依然可以
-I could have been with her!  -You still can.
你可以回家 Juliet 陪伴她走过最后的日子
You can go home, Juliet, be with her in her final days,
你也可以留下 帮助我解决问题
or you can stay here and help me with our problem.
我为什么要留下?
Why would I stay?
因为我可以帮你治好你妹妹
Because if you do, I will cure your sister's cancer.
我应该相信你吗?
I'm supposed to take that on faith?
你在这里六个月了
You've been here for six months.
你做了广泛的研究
You've done extensive workups on all of us.
-你有发现癌症吗?  -那是因为在这里
-Have you seen even a trace of cancer?  -That's here!
而你不肯把我妹妹带来
And being that you won't let me bring my sister here,
-我就需要更多...  -Jacob说他会照顾好自己的
-I'm gonna need more...  -Jacob said he would take care of it himself.
除非你不信任他
Unless, of course, you don't have faith in him.
岛上的每个女人都需要你
Every woman on this island needs you.
如果你留下
If you choose to stay,
我向你保证
I promise you,
我们会治好Rachel的
we will save Rachel's life.
相信她? 她是他们的人
Trust her? She's one of them.
不再是了 他们把她扔下了
Not anymore. They left her behind.
-是吗? 那他们去哪儿了?  -我也不知道
-Oh, yeah? Where'd they go?  -I told you. I don't know.
-也许我们最好问问她  -她自己也不知道
-Maybe we better ask her.  -She doesn't know either.
我有个主意  让伊拉克人去对付她
Here's a wacky idea. Let's sic our resident Iraqi on her,
-做他擅长的 然后看她怎么说  -我不在这么做了
-let him do what he does,then see what she says.  -I don't do that anymore.
这样不是很好吗?
Well, ain't that convenient?
但我不相信她 Jack 如果她真的那么无辜...
But I don't trust her, Jack. If she's so innocent...
那她为什么不回答我们的问题呢?
why won't she answer our questions?
-先给她点时间 她也受惊吓了  -要多少时间?
-Just give her some time. She's afraid.  -How much time?
-我相信她就足够了  -这还不够
-Look, the fact that I trust her should be enough.  -It's not.
Locke去哪儿了?
Where did Locke go?
他在炸了那潜艇之后 就和他们走了...
He went with them, right after he destroyed the sub...
那艘潜艇原本可以带我离开这里
The sub that was gonna take me off this island.
-什么?  -他们让你走?
-What?  -They were gonna let you go?
-是啊  -谁说的?
-Yeah.  -Said who?
Ben
Ben...
-你还救了他的命  -Sawyer 别说了
-Whose life you saved.  -Sawyer, lay off.
该让那暴眼杂种去死的
Shoulda let that bug-eyed bastard die!
-他这么做是为了我们  -听起来更像是为了自己
-He did it for us.  -Sounds like he did it for him.
你有什么要问我的吗?
Is there something you wanna ask me?
是啊  Jack
你为什么要为他们的人辩护呢?
I wanna ask you why you're fighting every single one of us and sticking up for one of them?
我在那里一直都在寻找
I spent every moment over there
离开这里的办法 我是在帮助我们所有人
trying to find a way off this island.I was trying to help all of us.
我想让大家得救
I was trying to get us rescued.
Clarie有点不对劲!
Something's wrong with Claire!
Clarie?
抓住她  抓住她
Grab her, grab her.
把她抱起来
Let's get her up. Let's get her up.
她这样有多久了?
How long has she been like this?
她早上有些不舒服
She started feeling bad this morning.
我们回来之前 她有这些症状吗?
Before we got back, was she showing any symptoms at all?
-不 她那时很好  -她喝水了吗 她有喝足够的水了吗?
-No,she was fine.  -What about water?Has she been drinking enough water?
我想是的 好了 把她头抬起来
I think so, yeah. All right, keep that head up.
她怎么了?
What happened to her?
他说"你关心什么?"
He said, "what do you care?"
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我要你去找Jack
I need you to go and get Jack.
他现在很忙
He's busy right now.
求你了  我得和他谈谈
Please, I have to talk to him.
有什么事吗?
You wanna tell me why you need Jack?
因为我知道Claire是怎么了
Because I think I know what's wrong with Claire.
怎么会?
Why?
因为这是我对她做的
Because I did it to her.
觉得有些不对劲吗?
Giving you a bad feeling in your stomach?
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
Clarie的免疫系统已经受到损坏
Claire's immune system is turning on her.
她在血液治疗中
She's having a latent reaction
-出现了反应  -什么治疗?
-to a medication in her bloodstream.  -What medication?
治疗的目的是让她
It was designed to keep her alive
-能在分娩后活下来  -谁设计的?
-during the late stages of her pregnancy.  -Designed by who?
我
By me.
不知什么原因 这里的女人都不能生育
For some reason the women here can't have babies.
母亲的身体"拒绝"怀孕
The mother's body turns on the pregnancy,
认为是某种入侵者
treats it as a foreign invader.
我看着这些不断的发生
I saw it happen over and over.
在这座岛上的每个孕妇都会死...
Every pregnant woman on this island died...
当然  直到Clarie的出现
That is,every pregnant woman until Claire.
你对她做了什么?
What did you do to her?
我们中的一个人潜入了你们的营地
One of our people infiltrated your camp
采集血样
and began taking blood samples
就在飞机失事后不久
right after your plane crashed.
Ethan
即使Clarie不是在这座岛上受孕的
Even though Claire didn't conceive on this island,
我们发现她的情况和这里其他孕妇是一样的
we found that her symptoms were consistent with previous mothers,
-我们只想救她的命  -通过绑架她?
-so we tried to save her life.  -By kidnapping her?
那本不该发生的
No, that wasn't supposed to happen.
她原本在我们的控制范围内 我发现了一种血清
She was our control case.I had developed a serum that
可以让她的身体回到从前的状态
I thought would reverse what was happening to her.
Ethan负责注射
Ethan was administering the injections.
但你们发现了他原本不在飞机上
Then you found out that he wasn't on the plane.
人数统计...我问了所有人
The census... I interviewed everyone.
有一个人不在名单里
One of them isn't in the manifest.
他不在飞机上
He wasn't on the plane.
所以他改变了计划
So... he improvised.
你们好
Hello there.
他自己绑架了她
He kidnapped her on his own.
那不在计划之中
That was never the plan.
我知道这不可相信
Look, I know how this sounds,
但没有那些注射 Clarie早就死了
but without those injections, Claire would have died.
没有了那些血清她会出现症状
Without the serum, she's going into a form of withdrawal,
如果我不及时帮她注射
and if I don't treat her quickly,
她的免疫系统将彻底崩溃
her immune system could shut down entirely.
Jack 我能挽救她 我所需要的就是血清
Jack, I can fix this.I just need the serum.
Ethan在山洞那边
Ethan kept a stash of medical supplies
有一些医疗用具
near the caves where you used to live.
如果我现在就去的话
If I go right now,
我还能及时赶回来
I can be back before it's too late.
就这样吧
Do it.
快去吧
Get moving.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
床上...和你在一起
In bed... with you.
那你以前在哪里?
And where were you?
我刚意识到...
I was just realizing...
到明天我就在这个岛上整整3年了
that tomorrow I will have been on this island for three years.
那我得做个蛋糕了
Then I better bake a cake.
呆在这儿
Stay here.
那是什么?
What have you got there?
Karl给我拿来了X光片
Karl developed some x-rays for me.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
早上好 Juliet
Morning, Juliet.
好啊
Hi.
我能进来吗?
Can I come in?
当然
Of course.
我刚读完"Carrie"
I was just finishing "Carrie."
我不知道你为什么选这本
I still don't know why you picked it,
-但这真让人压抑  -你有个肿瘤
-but, boy, is it depressing.  -You have a tumor.
什么? 当你说你背痛时
What? When you told me about your back pain,
我说要给你照X光
I said that I would take some x-rays
看看是否是小骨折还是脊椎间盘突出
to see if it was a small fracture or a herniated disc,
但那不是你的问题
but that's not your problem.
在L4椎骨上有个很大的肿瘤
Your problem is a large tumor surrounding your L4 vertebra.
你很惊讶
You're surprised.
你刚告诉我我得了癌症
You've just told me that I have cancer.
我当然很惊讶
Of course I'm surprised.
不  我告诉你你有个肿瘤
No, I told you that you had a tumor.
-你为什么那么害怕?  -我没有害怕
-Why are you scared?  -I'm not scared.
你为什么要害怕 Ben?
Why are you scared, Ben?
你说过在这座岛上没有人得过癌症
You said no one on this island ever had cancer.
-你告诉我...  -我知道我告诉你什么
-You told me that...  -I know what I told you.
你告诉我你能治好的
You told me you could fix it.
-你说你能治好我妹妹的 你骗了我  -不 我没骗你
-You said that you cured my sister.You lied to me.  -No,I did not lie to you.
如果你能治好癌症 你怎么会得上的呢?
If you can cure cancer, then why do you have it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我要和她谈谈 我要和Rachel谈谈
I wanna talk to her. I wanna talk to Rachel.
-我要和她谈谈 就现在!  -这是不可能的 Juliet
-I wanna talk to her now!  -That's not gonna happen, Juliet,
但我能保证 Rachel现在很好
but I can promise you that Rachel is fine.
-你没有治好她!  -不!
-You never cured her!  -I did!
-你是个骗子!  -不 Juliet
-You're a liar! -No, Juliet
你对我撒了谎!
You lied to me!
我告诉你的都是真的!
I told you the truth!
我保证过你
I gave you my word.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
我想回家 Ben 求你了
I wanna go home, Ben. Please.
你就不能让我走吗?
Can't you please just let me go home?
不行
No.
站在那儿别动!
Step away from the case!
-听我说Sayid  -退后
-Listen to me, Sayid...  -Step back.
都是些医疗用具 他们能救Claire
It's full of medical supplies. They're for Claire.
Jack都知道的
Jack knows all about it.
Jack现在不在这儿吧?
Jack ain't here right now, is he?
我说的都是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
你说过你把一切都告诉我
You said earlier if you told me everything you knew,
我会杀了你的
I'd kill you.
现在我要来验证一下
I'm going to test the validity of that statement.
他的意思是 "谈谈"
He means, "talk."
我们没时间了
We don't have time for this.
那我们取消其他安排
We cleared our schedules.
我们有的是时间
We got all the time in the world.
有意思的是...
You know, it's interesting...
你们两成了这个营地的警察
that you two are now the camp's moral police.
我很好奇 Sayid
I'm curious, Sayid.
什么时候你才会
How long was it before
告诉海滩上的人
you told everyone on that beach
你这一辈子折磨过多少人?
exactly how many people you've tortured in your life?
他们知道Basra市的事吗?
Do they know about Basra?
我很确定你来
And I'm sure the first thing
这里的第一件事 James
you did when you got here, James,
是告诉大家
was to gather everyone in a circle
在你登机之前的那个夜晚
and tell them about the man you shot in cold blood
你是怎么冷血的杀害那个人的
the night before you got on the plane.
我们为何不跳过
So why don't we just skip the part
你们作为"正义先锋"的部分?
where you two pretend to be righteous?
我要及时把这些送到Claire身边
I'm taking that medication back to Claire,
你们要让我走
and you're gonna let me,
因为如果她得不到这些
because if she doesn't get it,
她会死的
she's gonna die.
难道你们还想手上沾
And the last thing
更多鲜血吗?
that either of you need right now is more blood on your hands.
Goodwin! Ethan 一定还有幸存者
Goodwin! Ethan, there may actually be survivors,
你们假装是他们的一员 一个受到惊吓的乘客
and you're one of'em... a passenger. You're in shock.
观察  注意 不要暴露身份
Listen. Learn. Don't get involved.
三天之内我要所有的乘客名单
I want lists in three days.
看来我已经退出读书俱乐部了
So I guess I'm out of the book club.
Juliet  Juliet
我今天早上还在找你
I was looking for you this morning.
我们需要谈谈
You and I need to talk.
现在吗?
Now?
我们还有些时间 这很重要
We have some time. It's important.
我们一起走走
Take a walk with me.
Mikhail 我们到了
Mikhail, we're here.
他从不打开对讲机
He never has his walkie on.
我们在这儿干什么?
What are we doing here?
我要给你看样东西
Something I need to show you.
我是Ben! Juliet和我在一起!
It's Ben! I'm here with Juliet!
我们要进来了! 别乱开枪
We're approaching the house! Don't shoot us.
快进来吧!
Well, hurry up, then!
你看见了吗?
Did you see it?
一架飞机从天而降 Mikhail
A plane fell out of the sky, Mikhail.
我们当然看见了
Of course we saw it.
有什么消息吗?
What do you have so far?
大西洋航空公司815航班 从悉尼起飞
Oceanic flight 815,left Sydney, Australia,
目的地是洛杉矶
headed for Los Angeles,
包括机组人员共324人
324 people on board, including the flight crew.
我要每名乘客的所有详细资料
I want detailed files on every single passenger.
已经在办了
Already working on it.
可以连接上Acadia公园的Richard吗?
Can we uplink to Richard in Acadia park, please?
昨天你叫我骗子
Yesterday you called me a liar.
我很伤心
I was hurt by that.
你好 Richard 能听见我吗?
Hello, Richard. Can you hear me?
注意日期  是今天
Notice today's date.
这是现场直播 好了 Richard
This is live. Okay, Richard.
我的上帝! 我的上帝!
Oh, my God.
我的上帝!
两年前
A little over two years ago,
令许多人惊讶的是
to everyone's surprise,
Rachel的癌症完全消失
Rachel's cancer went into complete remission.
不久以后  她生下了这个健康的小男孩
Shortly after, she gave birth to a healthy baby boy.
她为他取名叫Julian
His name is Julian.
好了  谢谢你 Richard
Okay, thank you, Richard.
你尽快回来
You'll want to get back here as soon as you can.
我们有些新客人
We may have some new visitors.
不不不!
Oh, god! No,
不!
no!
我不是骗子 Juliet
I'm not a liar, Juliet.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
我们的协议不是这样的
That's not our agreement.
你要待在这儿直到完成了你的使命
You need to stay here until your work is finished.
这不可能  孕妇不断的死亡
It's impossible. The mothers keep dying.
那我们就要找更多的母亲
Then we'll find more mothers.
谁知道呢?
Who knows?
也许那飞机上就有一个
Maybe there's even one on that plane.
等等 你在做什么?
Wait. What are you doing?
不准她碰Clarie  这都是她对Clarie的好事
She's not touching her. She's the one who did this to her.
-她能帮她Charlie  -谁说的? 她吗?你怎么能相信她?
-She can help her.  -Says who? her? How can you even trust her?
我相信她
I do trust her.
你相信我吗?
Do you trust me?
是的
Yeah.
几分钟就好了  好吗?
Just give us a couple minutes here, okay?
多久能起效?
How long before this takes effect?
几小时后就能得出结果
We should see results in a few hours.
Juliet...
如果这不管用的话
If this doesn't work,
如果她出了什么事的话...
if something happens to her...
我就不会在保护你了
I'm not gonna be able to protect you anymore.
你只能靠自己了
You'll be on your own.
我已经是一人了 Jack
I'm already on my own, Jack.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我拿了鞋帆布和毯子
I've got a tarp, couple of blankets,
还有枕头
airline pillows.
这不多
It's not much,
但...怎么也是起步了
but...it'll get you started.
Clarie醒了
Claire's awake.
那边有个斜坡 我们都去乘凉
There's a lean-to that we've been using for shade,
而且大家都同意
and everyone says that it'd be all right
你在那边扎营
if you set up camp there for now.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们都是好人
They're good people,
他们愿意补偿对你的怀疑
and they're willing to give you the benefit of the doubt.
但他们还是需要一些答案
But eventually they're gonna need some answers.
为什么你不需要?
Why don't you?
你一直在说他们
You keep talking about them.
为什么我不需要对你做出解释呢?
why don't I ever have to explain myself to you?
你在那里
You were there.
当潜艇爆炸时
You were standing right next to me
你就在那里...
when that submarine exploded...
在那一刻 我从你的眼里看出
And in that moment, I saw it in your eyes.
你比任何一个人
You wanna get off this island
都更加想要离开这座岛
more than anything else in the world.
你也是我们的一员
That makes you one of us.
我们再回顾一下
Let's go over it again.
-我知道该怎么做  -我们再温习一遍 确保一下
-I know what to do.  -Let's go over it again,just to be sure.
我把Austen拖进丛林
I drag Austen out into the jungle,
然后把我和她拷在一起
handcuff myself to her,
然后告诉她我也和她一样被放了瓦斯弹
then tell her I was gassed just like she was.
-如果她发现你在撒谎呢?  -我会承认
-And if she catches you in the lie?  -I'll admit to it,
告诉她这是让她信任我的唯一方法
tell her it was the only way to earn her trust.
很好  然后呢?
Good. What then?
他们会把我带回海滩
They'll take me back to the beach.
我知道你想让我去那里
I know you want me to go there,
但在我们对他们做的所有事后
but after everything we've done to them,
这将是个问题
it's going to be a problem.
我们已经启动了Clarie体内的植入设备
We've activated the implant in Claire.
48小时内她会出现症状
She should be symptomatic within the next 48 hours.
等你到了营地
By the time you get to that camp,
你将要有个很大的危机要解决
you'll have a nice big crisis to solve.
我需要医疗用具
I'll need supplies.
Pryce已经在办了
Pryce is already on his way.
他会把箱子放在Ethan原来的藏身地点
He'll hide the case at Ethan's old drop point.
告诉Jack你能救她
Tell Jack that you can save her.
她会信任你
He trusts you.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
我很好
I'm fine.
一周后再见
See you in a week.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■